http://www.legacyproductsinc.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Commitment & Information UseLegacy is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process your order and/or to provide a personalized shopping experience. The collected information is never sold or rented. Based on the information you’ve provided, we may send you special offers, new product details and other exciting Legacy Products news by postal mail or email… although you can always opt out at any time. We may also monitor customer activity and site usage to help us better serve our visitors.
Website Use By using LegacyProductsInc.com, you consent to the collection and use of the information obtained by Legacy and to the terms of this policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the website. Legacy Products Inc. is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites that may be linked to or from LegacyProductsInc.com.
Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Legacy Products Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Legacy’s sole discretion. Legacy encourages visitors to frequently check this page for changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Subscribe/UnsubscribeIf you would like to add your name, correct your information or remove your name from our mailing list, please email us or write us at:
info@LegacyProductsInc.com
Legacy Products Inc.120 West Main StreetPO Box 267Cambridge City, IN 47327 USA
Personal Information AccessExcept as otherwise provided in this policy or by law, personally identifiable information is only shared within Legacy Products Inc. From time to time, we may engage third parties to provide services related to the maintenance and operation of the website. In connection with the services, the provider may have access to information provided by users of the website. A service provider's use of such information is restricted by confidentiality agreements between Legacy Products Inc. and such provider.
Shopping Cart Security
Legacy Products Inc. uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer software) to encrypt your credit card and account information and securely send it to the credit card company and authorizer during the order process. To protect against unauthorized account use, be sure to Log Out when you have completed the purchasing process.
CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Legacy Products Inc. uses cookies to help Legacy identify and track visitors, their usage of the Legacy website, their website access preferences and store products in the cart throughout their visit and for up to 8 hours between visits. Cookies are REQUIRED to store producst in the cart, checkout and log into the site. Legacy visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Legacy’s website, with the drawback that certain features of Legacy’s websites (including adding items to the cart, checking out and logging in) may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Manual orders can always be placed by printing out our Order Form and contacting us by phone, mail or fax with your order.
About UsOur Story
In the News
Testimonials
Legacy Wish List
The MediKin Story
Printable InformationProduct Line Brochure
Asthma Program Flyer
Infection Control/Cleaning
Purchase Orders (US Only)
U.S. Patent Numbers 5,411,437, 5,795,157, 7,284,986 and 5,853,293
© 2020 Legacy Products, Inc.
Newsletter -
Sign up & get 10% Off + Free Gift!
Enter Email Address
Privacy Policy
